# Francesco Spata

## **Full Stack Engineer**

I am currently pursuing my career as a software developer, thanks to the specialized training received through the progetto CODE and Codecademy. This path has prepared me for a professional role in this sector after obtaining a Bachelor's degree in Political Science, a significant milestone achieved following several years of work experience in other fields. In the future, I aspire to continue developing my skills in Web Development and explore new opportunities that allow me to grow both professionally and personally.

#### **CONTACTS**

- franc.spata@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/francesco-spata

**L** +39 392 6648869

#### **SKILLS**

- TypeScript, Next.js, React, Node.js, MySQL
- · Git. GitHub
- Online content evaluation and indexing
- Italian native, English C1

#### **EDUCATION**

Professional diploma at Codecademy, Full Stack Engineer

Professional diploma at CODE, Backend Developer

#### Università degli studi di Catania

Bachelor's degree in Political Science (2019 - 2023)

#### **Specialization Course MSU**

Michigan State University - Scholarship (2020 - 2021)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Full Stack Engineer

2023 - Present

Freelancer at Fiverr

- Design, Development and Deployment
- Work independently with a schedule

#### ADS Rater

2022 - 06/2024

TELUS INTERNATIONAL, Google Partner

- Daily work analyzing user query data for Google and evaluating advertisements.
- Building daily schedules independently and coordinating with teams.

#### Bartender

2016 - 2023

- Extensive experience in team work and shift work.
- Excellent public relations skills